[Music]
I used to dream about buying a bigger
house sitting on top of some Hill
losing sleep about feeling my bank
account wondering if I ever will but the
older I get I just care less and less
about keeping up with people named Jones
if you don't fill it up with somebody
that you love it ain't never wanna feel
like home
there's always gonna be a higher high
you could Chase for the rest of your
life greener grass in the yard next door
or shine up Chevy little newer than
yours you're never gonna feel it empty
cup if what you got still not enough
us that don't live in bigger houses
I can hear the kids making Little
Footsteps running down the hallway
upstairs
I can see the dogs playing in the
backyard through the kitchen window
right there maybe that's kind of more
about a swing on a porch holding her
while the sun disappears why would I
wanna be anywhere else in the world
sitting right here there's always
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
there's always gonna be a high yeah
you could Chase for the rest of your
life
green of grass in the yard next door a
shined up Chevy little New World in
yours
[Music]
there has to have houses the thing about
happiness I found is you don't live in
bigger houses
[Music]